He doesn't look like one at all
Starting today
no one will ever easily mistake
Fu Chenzhou for a regular bodyguard
This man is much harder
to deal with than I thought
Mr Fu you stood out a bit too much today
I tried to keep it brief
You call that keeping it brief
I haven't even brought up the real issue
The Gu family's cash flow is
tighter than it seemed in the meeting
How did you know
They were in too much of a rush to
push the payment schedule forward
Those who truly aren't short of money
wouldn't be so afraid of a review
Mr Lin is there an issue with this file
What's this guy's name
Fu Chenzhou Su Mengyao's new husband
What's the rush
Chairman please look at this person first
Who is this
Fu Chenzhou
His surname is Fu too
Yes public records show his name is Fu Chenzhou